I'm not even up out my bed yet but I just need to say this to start the day off right
not too much on black folks I've been seeing a lot of white folks lately including their content
creation criticism of black folks particularly non-politically aligned black folks okay
and I know that you got folks like Jay-Z you got folks like Beyonce you got folks like Oprah out
here I know you right they foul leave it to us leave it to us you genuinely don't have any time
to address black folks because there are so many white people with actual systemic power
that you need to be talking about you don't even have time to get to the black folks we got it
often these criticisms are lacking cultural competency we got it and they create spaces
for predominantly non-black audiences to sit and talk ish about a black person which inevitably
is going to get racist we got it leave them to us leave them to us you got your work cut out for you
with your folks and you need to stay focused on that have a good day
cut out the corporate middlemen and purchase my music directly from me head to amandadiva.bandcamp.com
and pay whatever price you want for truth translator this ain't a movement it's movement music